24小时
第三季  第23集
前情提要
总统先生 关于艾伦·米利肯的死 我知道你撒了谎
Mr. President, with respect to the death of Alan Milliken, I know you lied.
你告诉警方雪莉在案发当时和你在一起
You told the police Sherry was with you at the time of Milliken's death.
她留在药瓶上的指纹能证明你在撒谎
Her fingerprints on this prescription bottle prove otherwise.
你想怎么样?
What do you want?
你的辞职
Your resignation.
雪莉只有这一个证据 是吗?
Without this, Sherry's got nothing, right?
我可以打给福克斯顿 他能摆平这一切
Now, I can call Foxton, and he can make this all disappear.
你的意思是偷走证据
You mean steal evidence.
杰克 我听说托尼私自带走了简 桑德斯
Jack, I just heard Tony took Jane Saunders out of the building without authorization.
桑德斯抓了米歇尔
Saunders has Michelle.
他要求换回他女儿
He wants to trade her for his daughter.
托尼 把枪放在仪表盘上
Tony, put that gun on the dash.
你帮我完成交换 我就去自首
You help me make this trade, I will turn myself in.
进监狱或是什么都无所谓
Go to prison, whatever is gotta happen.
我们还没发现桑德斯 重复 还没发现桑德斯
We don't have a visual on Saunders. I repeat we don't have a visual on Saunders
保持待命 全体待命
Keep your teams down. Stay down.
我不要
I can't.
简 没关系的 快过来
Jane, it's ok, come here.
A组和B组行动
Team A and B move.
立即行动
Move now.
斯蒂芬
Stephen.
我被火力压制了
I am pinned down.
桑德斯有直升机接应
Saunders has a helicopter.
请求空中支援
Call in air support now.
还有11瓶病毒瓶下落不明
11 vials of the virus are unaccounted for.
它们在哪?
Where are they?
这可没你想得那么简单 杰克
It's not going to be that simple, Jack.
我是杰克·鲍尔
This is Jack Bauer.
桑德斯被捕了
Saunders is in custody.
以下事件发生于11:00点到12:00点之间
The following takes place between 11:00 am and 12:00 pm.
我们在桑德斯的电脑上确认
We just got verification from Saunders' computer.
全国还有11瓶病毒
There's 11 vials across the country
还要多久才能锁定位置?
How long till you can give us their location?
我不敢肯定
I am not sure I can.
桑德斯采用了非常复杂的加密程序
Saunders applied a sophisticated decryption overlay.
非法登陆会导致所有文件被删除
An unauthorized access will auto erase the file structure.
-我会尽力  -好的
-I will keep trying.  -Ok.
其他11个病毒瓶在哪?
Where are the 11 vials?
你只是在浪费时间 我可不会把资料放在那里面
You are wasting your time, and I am not foolish enough to have that information in there.
那些病毒在哪?
Where are the vials?
在那些有同样信念的人手上
In the hands of dedicated men, true believers.
什么信念?
Believers in what?
世界和平的最大绊脚石就是这个国家
That's the greatest threat to world peace comes from this country.
因为你 不远处酒店里800个无辜民众正面临死亡甚至已经死去
There's a hotel not far from here where 800 innocent people are dead or dying because of you.
他们也是你所谓的世界和平的绊脚石吗?
Were they a threat to your world peace?
美国必须妥协
The United States must be forced to retreat within it's own borders.
那些人不过是战争的首批受害者
Those people are simply the first casualties of war.
你到底怎么了 斯蒂芬?
What happened to you, Stephen?
我被自己所卖命的人抛弃了
I was abandoned by the people I worked for.
迟早有一天你的下场会和我一样
As you will be some day.
一小时后 你们就会明白
But my message will be heard in less than 1 hour.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我的同伴在我被捕后就会释放病毒
My couriers have been instructed to release the virus at noon.
它们没有安全模式也不可能被召回
They are in fail safe mode and they can't be recalled.
告诉我他们在哪 我们要制止他们
Tell us where they are, we will stop them.
那也成 但你要答应我提出的条件
That is possible, but only if you agree to my terms.
什么条件?
What are your terms?
有架私人喷气机在范奈斯机场等我
I have a private jet waiting at Van Nuys airport.
我需要总统签发的通行证 以保证我能安全的到达北非
I need to be on it with presidential guarantee of safe passage to North Africa.
这不可能
Never going to happen.
那成千上万的人就会死去
Then hundreds of thousands will die.
我知道你在想什么 杰克
I know what you are thinking, Jack.
波斯尼亚的特务花了两年时间想让我屈服
But the Bosnian secret police worked on me for 2 years and couldn't break me.
你认为你可以在不到1小时的时间内做到?
Do you really think you will be able to do it in less than an hour?
让我上飞机 杰克
Get me on that plane, Jack.
你别无选择
You don't have a choice.
把简 桑德斯带来
Bring me Jane Saunders.
把枪给我 托尼
I'm gonna need your gun, Tony.
搜他身
Frisk him.
嘿
Hey.
-你没必要这样  -我收到上头命令
-You don't have to do that.  -I have got my orders.
-你客气点 他是自己人  -不再是了
-You take it easy. He's one of us.  -Not any more.
怎么回事?
What's going on?
我收到命令前来逮捕阿尔梅达
My orders are to take Almeida into custody.
命令来自布拉德 哈蒙德
That's straight from Brad Hammond at Division.
很抱歉 托尼
I am sorry, Tony.
我们暂时无能为力
There's nothing we can do right now.
你管好这就行了 杰克
Just take care of business, Jack.
我会没事的
I'll be all right.
他说你要见我?
He said you wanted to see me?
我要你和你父亲谈谈
I need you to speak with your father.
你要我说什么?
What do you want me to say?
尽量温和一点
Try and make it personal.
多和他交流
Try to connect with him.
告诉他你害怕 你不想他这么做
Tell him you are scared that you don't want him to do this.
我试试看
I will try.
我知道将发生什么事 我也知道你可以制止这件事
I know what's going to happen, and I know you can stop it.
求你了
Please.
我知道他们会利用你来控制我
I wont let them use you to manipulate me.
抛开已经发生的事
Despite everything that's happened.
我仍然爱你
I love you.
我现在请求你 不要让这件事发生
And I asking you, please don't let this happen.
这根本就毫无意义
This doesn't make any sense.
你觉得不和情理是因为你没看见我所经历的事情
It doesn't make any sense to you because you haven't seen what I have seen.
你不会明白的
You don't understand.
我知道你认为你受的罪是政府带来的
I know you think what happened to you is the governments fault, and maybe it is.
但那些面临死亡的人是无辜的
But the people who are going to die are innocent.
这样是很惨 简
Ant that's tragic, Jane.
但这是我们改变现实的唯一方法 而这一切也必须改变
But it has to happen for things to change and they must change.
你这么能做出这种事?
How can you do something like this?
我这么做都是为了你
I am doing it for your sake.
为了我?
For my sake?
为了你和你的孩子
For you and your children.
为了这世界上的其他人能有更好的生存环境
And after it, the world will be a better place.
求你了 爸爸
Please, Dad.
求你了
Please.
求你别这么做
Please, don't do this.
简 我不指望你现在就能明白
Jane, I don't expect you to understand now.
但总有一天你会明白的
But one day you will.
然后你会回头感谢我所做的一切
And you will look back and you will thank me for what I have done.
真的
Yeah.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my god.
简
Jane.
我们行动 准备好直升机
We are on the move, get the choppers ready.
喂
Hello.
雪莉 我是大卫
Sherry, it's David.
你好 大卫
Hello, David.
我仔细想了一下
I have been thinking things over.
基勒给了你什么 你想得到什么?
What Keeler offered you, how did you put it?
一个高位?
A seat at the table?
没错 差不多吧
Yeah, something like that.
倒不如我给你一个高位
Well, there may be a seat at my table.
现在才说是不是太晚了点 大卫
It's a little too late for that, David.
雪莉 我认为你仔细听我说的话对我们都有好处
Sherry, I think it's in both our best interests for you to hear what I have to offer.
好 我洗耳恭听
All right, I am listening.
不 不是在电话里说
No, not on the phone.
要面谈
In person.
在哪见面?
Where, then?
市区 林肯公园的棒球场
The Oakcliff Building, downtown.
知道了
I know it.
好 25分钟后在那见
Good. I will meet you there in 25 minutes.
我可赶不及 大卫
That's a short notice, David.
但你会准时到的
But you will be there.
你没权利要求任何事
You are in no position to be making demands here.
雪莉 我的行程是早就排好的
Sherry, I have a schedule to keep.
如果我贸然改变行程 就会引起别人注意 你我都不想这样吧
If I start changing things around, it will attract attention and I don't think either one of us wants that.
好吧 大卫
All right, David.
我倒想听听你要说什么
I will hear what you have to say.
好
Fine.
喂
Yeah.
她很快就会来见我
She should be leaving soon to meet me.
我就知道她会来的
I know shed go for it.
哦 她以为她掌控一切
Oh, she's enjoying having me over a barrel.
从她的语气中就能听出来
I could hear it in her voice.
别担心 大卫
Don't worry about that, David.
她一走我们就可以去找那个瓶子
If we can find this prescription bottle, all her leverage is gone.
你们需要多少时间
How long will you need in the house.
时间越充足 找到的几率就越高
The more time we have, the better our chance of finding it.
我会尽量拖住她的
I will do whatever I can to keep her there with me.
好
All right.
韦恩 一定要找到
Wayne, find it.
看看你干的好事
Take a look at your handiwork.
是你害死了这些人 斯蒂芬
You murdered these people, Stephen.
有些还是一家人
Whole families.
有些时候为了灭火必须先放火
Sometimes a fire needs to be lit in order to put out another fire.
我不要听你的谬论
I don't want to hear your justification.
这件事到此为止
This is over.
你现在马上告诉我其他的病毒在哪
You are going to tell me how to find the rest of the vials now.
否则你就把我送进酒店?
Or you'll send me inside the hotel?
我已经准备好去死了 杰克
I am prepared to die for my cause, Jack.
对 我知道
Yeah, I know.
-蔡斯  -请讲 杰克
-Chase.  -Yeah, Jack.
-带过来  -收到
-Come in.  -Copy that.
你要干什么 杰克?
What are you doing, Jack?
为什么把我带来这?
Why did you bring me here?
你该问你父亲 这取决于他
Ask your father, it's up to him.
爸?
Dad?
告诉我怎么找到那些运货人 斯蒂芬
Tell me how to find your couriers, Stephen.
否则我就把你女儿扔进酒店
Or I am going to put her in that building.
你不会的 她和这事完全没有关系
You wouldn't dare. She has nothing to do with this.
这同样和那些死去的人没有关系
Neither do the people in those body bags.
我会不惜一切来阻止你释放病毒
I am going to do everything I have to stop you from releasing more of this virus.
你怎么能这样?
How could you do this?
我给你一次机会选择
I am going to give you one chance.
不 你不会这么做的
No, you are not.
告诉我怎么找到他们
Tell me how I find them.
你知道你不能这么做 杰克
You know you can't do this, Jack.
你是政府的探员
You are a government agent.
把她送进去
Send her in.
马上把她送进去
Take her inside now.
不
No.
爸 让他们停下 爸爸 求你了
Dad, stop them. Dad, stop them.
别这样
Stop it. Stop it.
爸 求你了
Dad, please.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
你女儿所受的一切痛苦都因你而起
Everything that happens to your daughter is because of you.
爸 让他们停下 不 不
Dad, stop, no, no, no.
把她放出来 杰克
Get her out of there, Jack.
杰克 把她放出来
Jack, get her out of there.
病毒在哪?
Where are the vials?
放她出来
Get her out of there.
怎么找到病毒?
How do I find the vials?
爸
Dad.
放了她
Let her go.
照我说的做 杰克!
Do as I say now, Jack!
一旦你女儿染上病毒 我会让你看着她死去
When your daughter is infected, I am going to make you watch her die.
鲍尔 放开她
Bauer, let her go.
放了她
Let her go.
你时间不多了 斯蒂芬
You are running out of time, Stephen.
斯蒂芬 你没时间了
Stephen, you are out of time.
停下 停下 停下来 我全告诉你
Stop, stop, stop, I will tell you.
别伤害她了
Just don't harm her.
我怎么能找到病毒?
How do I find the vials?
每份病毒都绑定了全球定位系统 这样我可以在释放前追踪它们
Each one is tagged with a GPS locator chip so that I can track them right up until t he moment they are released.
定位编码是多少?
Where are the locator codes?
在我脑子了
In my head.
你都记下了?
You memorized all 11?
对 放她出来
Yeah, get her out of there.
把简从管道里带出来
Bring Jane out from the tunnel now.
我们走
Let's go.
杰克 我们找到了11个定位编码中的10个
Jack, we have picked up 10 of the 11 GPS signals coming off the vials.
为什么少了一个?
Why are we missing a signal?
不知道 我给的是正确的编码
I don't know. I gave you the correct codes.
第11瓶病毒在哪?
Where's the 11th vial?
洛杉矶
Los Angels.
目标是什么?
What's the target?
选择一个能够尽可能造成最大伤亡的公共场所
His instruction were to select a public place where maximum casualties would be inflicted.
他的名字?
What's his name?
我所知道的是亚瑟·拉本斯
I know him as Arthur Rabens.
但恐怕这不是他的真名
But I am assuming that's not his real name.
我们需要他的外貌特征
We need a description.
把他带回反恐局
Take him back to holding over at CTU.
我需要他马上能帮绘画专家画出图象
I want him working with a sketch artist immediately.
简怎么办?
What about Jane?
把她留在这
She stays here.
考夫曼
Kaufman.
亚当 我是杰克
Adam, it's Jack.
在所有数据库中查找亚瑟·拉本斯这号人
I need you to do an all agency search on the name Arthur Rabens.
桑德斯认为那是个假名
Saunders believes it might be a alias.
好 马上跟进 杰克
Ok, I am on it, Jack.
总部有没有派人来接替托尼?
Has district sent anyone over to replace Tony?
没错 布拉德 哈蒙德刚到这
Actually, yeah, Brad Hammond just got here right now.
好 让他听电话
Ok, let me speak to him.
稍等
One second.
哈蒙德先生
Mr. Hammond.
杰克·鲍尔在6号线要和你通话
I have Jack Bauer for you on line 6.
好 谢谢
Good, thank you.
杰克
Jack.
和你说一下反恐局的进度
I have been briefed on CTU activity to this point.
我们把病毒的消息通知了地方警局 卫生处等机构
We are relaying the coordinates of the 10 vials to local police, NHS and HazMat across the country.
但目前还无法确定第11瓶病毒的下落
But we still can't lock on a signal from the 11th vial.
第11瓶病毒在洛杉矶
The 11th vial is in Los Angeles.
持有它的人叫亚瑟·拉本斯
The couriers name is Arthur Rabens.
虽然桑德斯认为这是个化名
Although Saunders believes that that might be an alias.
攻击目标还为明确
There's no predetermined target.
他说的是实话吗
Did he tell you the truth.
没错 他以为如果他不合作我们会伤害他女儿
Yeah. Right now he thinks we are willing to kill his daughter if he doesn't cooperate.
但我们最好还是锁定那个信号
But our best bet is to lock on to that signal.
我知道每个人都在努力
I understand everyone in comm is working on it.
布拉德 我知道你刚抓了托尼·阿尔梅达
Brad, I know you took Tony Almeida into custody.
但现在他的妻子平安无事 我认为他能帮我们
But now that his wife is safe, I think he might be a real asset to us.
抱歉 杰克 我不认为这能有什么特别的处置
I am sorry, Jack, but there's not going to be any special treatment.
看在上帝的份上 布拉德
For Gods sakes, Brad.
四年半前 我和托尼现在的处境一模一样
Four and a half years ago, I was put in the exact same position as Tony's been put in today.
维克托里 德拉赞绑架了我妻子和女儿 我逃离反恐局去救她们
Victor Darzen kidnapped my wife and daughter, and I went outside of CTU to get them back.
但可没人把我关进监狱
And no one put me in prison.
这回情况不一样
The circumstances were different.
情况不一样 结果还是一样 我们会成功的
And the outcome will be the same, we will prevail.
整个行动差点因为他的行为而以失败告终
The entire operation was put at risk because of what he did.
这个行动一年前由我 盖尔和托尼一同策划的
This operation started a year ago with Gael, Tony and myself.
盖尔已经牺牲了 为了掩护身份我染上了毒瘾 而你现在却要把托尼送进监狱?
Gael gave his life, I became an addict just to maintain my cover, and now you are sending Tony to prison?
这可不对
It's wrong.
布拉德 你知道这样不对
Brad, it's wrong and you know it.
你应该给他个奖章而不是手铐
You should be putting a medal on him not handcuffs.
杰克 你可以在他的听证会上作证
Jack, you can testify at his hearing.
但现在我们还有要紧事做
Right now, we have got work to do.
米歇尔在哪?
Where's Michelle?
就在这
She's here.
我和她说两句吗?
Can I talk to her, please?
一步步来
First thing first.
普拉切基正从大法官那里过来给你录口供
Plachecki's coming over from the attorney Generals office to take your official statement.
你最好找个律师
You are entitled to have a lawyer present.
听着 我不需要律师 布拉德
Look, I don't need a lawyer, Brad.
我自作自受
I did what I did.
你做的事 最高可以判死刑 托尼
What you did, Tony, is punishable by the death penalty.
死刑?
Death penalty?
你认为呢?
What did you expect?
你犯的是叛国罪
You committed treason.
那不是我的本意
That was not my intent.
你协助杀害瑞恩 夏佩尔的犯人逃跑
You facilitated the escape of a man who was responsible for the death of Ryan Chappell.
这个人已经杀害了数百人
and almost a thousand civilians,
并且正威胁着数百万人的安全
who was contemplating killing millions of others.
你却想葬送我们唯一的筹码 把他女儿交还给他
Then you tried to neutralize the only leverage we had over him, by giving him back his daughter.
那最低刑罚是什么?
So what's the bottom line?
我会证明你工作很久了 并且大部分时间表现优秀
I will testify to the fact that your service record is long and for the most part, distinguished.
运气好的话 20年
With luck, the best you can hope for is 20 years.
雪莉现在应该出发了
Sherry should have left by now.
是的 她故意耗掉时间
Yeah, well, she's taking her time.
好让总统等她
So she can make the President wait.
韦恩·帕默尔
Wayne Palmer.
韦恩
Wayne.
我告诉你别打给我
I told you not to call me.
我没别人可找了
I don't have anyone else.
很抱歉 我现在帮不了你
I am sorry, but I can't help you right now.
警察马上就会回来逮捕我 韦恩 说我杀了艾伦
The police are coming back to arrest me, Wayne, for murdering Alan.
因为他们不相信雪莉曾经来过这
Because they don't believe that Sherry was here.
我知道发生过什么
I know what happened.
那你为什么不把真相告诉他们?
Then why didn't you tell them the truth?
我的律师说总统在帮雪莉掩饰
My lawyer says that the President is backing Sherry's story.
这是真的吗?
Is it true?
你哥哥在帮雪莉掩饰吗?
Is your brother covering for Sherry?
我不知道 朱莉娅
I don't know, Julia.
别对我说谎
Don't lie to me.
听着 我很抱歉 但我现在什么都帮不了你
Listen, I am sorry, but there's nothing I can do for you right now.
求你了
Please.
别挂电话
Just don't, don't hang up.
我保证一有空就打给你
I will call you as soon as I can, I promise.
韦恩
Wayne.
我很害怕
I am so scared.
我知道 我明白
I know, I know.
我们曾经相爱
We loved each other once.
帮帮我
Help me.
我必须挂了 朱莉娅
I have to go, Julia.
韦恩
Wayne.
抱歉
I am sorry.
我是总统的首席幕僚 但现在却在干入室行窃的勾当
Chief of Staff to the President of the United States and I am committing a burglary.
多么具有讽刺意味的一刻
It's an historic moment.
福克斯顿 一定不能让雪莉知道我们来过这
Foxton, Sherry can never know we were here.
照我说的做 她就绝对不会察觉
You do what I say, and she wont.
快找吧
Let's get to work.
杰克
Jack.
旧金山传来的抓捕录像
This is the tactical feed from San Francisco.
他们抓住了桑德斯的一个运货人
They are apprehending Saunders courier.
他停止呼吸了
He's not breathing.
他被击毙了
He's been neutralized.
狙击手击中他的头部
Sniper took him down with a head shot.
找到了
We have got it.
病毒瓶在匣子里
The vial is intact.
重复 找到病毒瓶了
Repeat, we have the vial.
找到一个 还有10个呢
One down, 10 to go.
厨房找过了吗?
You check the kitchen?
对 找了两次了
Yeah, for the second time.
什么都没发现
There is nothing there.
看来帕默尔女士相信化学药品能让她活的更好
Well, it looks like Mrs. Palmer believes in better living through chemistry.
但这些药瓶没有一个是米利肯的
But none of the bottles are Milliken's.
见鬼
Damn it.
放松
Relax.
如果她把东西藏在这 肯定会找到的
If she's hidden it here, well find it.
你为什么这么确定?
How can you be so sure?
因为她不是专家 我是
Because she's not a professional, and I am.
雪莉
Sherry.
大卫
David.
一起走走吧
Let's take a walk.
事实上 我更希望开门见山
Well, actually, I just wanted to get to the point.
你决定的怎么样了?
What is it that you have decided?
我决定给你想要的
I decided to give you what you want.
一个内阁部长的位置
A place in my administration.
嗯 这你已经在电话中暗示过了 既然我都来了 我希望你能说的更详细点
Well, that's what you implied over the phone, but I thought I was here so that you could be a little more specific.
你将成为内阁中的重要人物 涉足所有重大决定
You will be my de facto right hand, involved in all major decisions.
怎么个涉足法?
Involved how?
从会见各国大使到立法提案
On everything from ambassadorial appointments to legislative proposals,
你将成为我的高级顾问
you will be one of my primary consultants.
你的一个顾问?
One of your consultants?
没错
Right.
再见 大卫
Good bye, David.
怎么了? 你去哪?
Why? Where are you going?
回家 因为这谈话到此结束
Back home, because this conversation is over.
为什么?
Why?
那可不够
That's just not good enough.
我可不想做个跑龙套的让你召之即来挥之即去
I am not going to be relegated to some informal role so that you can ignore me whenever you choose.
那你到底想要什么?
Why don't you just tell me what you want?
我想要一个永久的位子 大卫 不仅在你的内阁里更在你的生活中
I want a permanent position, David, in your administration and in your life.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我想再做回你的妻子
I want to be your wife again.
你什么?
You what?
我并不指望能回到以前那么亲密的状态
I don't expect to have the kind of physical intimacy that we used to have,
虽然也许随着时间的推移还会再有
although maybe in time that will come,
但我真的很像再次做回大卫·帕默尔夫人
but I really want be Mrs. David Palmer again.
做第一夫人 在你身边 在华盛顿或是跟随你到任何地方
The first lady, right by your side in Washington wherever you go.
雪莉 我不知道该说什么好
Sherry, I don't know what to say.
你点头就行了
You can start by saying yes,
要么我永远离开
or I walk for good.
你准备好接受我做回你的妻子了吗?
Are you prepared to have me be your wife again?
是的
Yes.
真的吗?
Really?
哦 大卫
Oh, David.
哦 天哪
Oh, God.
我们得谈谈具体的细节
We should talk about the details.
找个适当的时机
Work out a timeline.
我们一起公开出现
How we expose this to the public.
等等
Wait a minute.
我知道你可没这么简单 大卫
I know you a little better than this, David.
有些不对劲
Something's not right here.
你把这变的这么简单
You are making this all too easy.
肯定还有什么别的原因
There's, there's something else going on.
我只是给你想要的
I am giving you what you asked for.
不 不 不 你不是
No, no, no, you are not.
你在耍我
You are toying with me.
我不知道为什么 说实话 我也不在乎
And I don't know why, and frankly, I don't care.
你就当我什么都没说过
You just consider my offer rescinded.
约翰 基勒将会成为美国的下一届总统
John Keeler will be the next President of the United States.
喂
Yeah.
她正赶回去
She's on her way back.
大卫 我们需要更多的时间
David, we need more time.
我们还什么都没找到
We haven't found anything yet.
听着 我已经尽力拖延她了
Look, I tried to keep her here as long as I could,
但她察觉出不对劲了
but she knew something was wrong.
韦恩 你必须马上离开
Wayne, you should leave.
东西还没找到
We are not done.
她很快就会回去 我们别无选择
She will be there soon, we have no choice.
大卫 等等
David, hold on.
这有个保险箱
There's a safe.
大卫 我们在密道里发现个保险箱
David, we found a safe in a hidden cellar.
你们来的及打开吗?
Can you open it in time?
能打开吗?
Can you get in?
它被固定在墙里 所以不能炸开
It's an Evans Stoller, so forget about cracking it.
这种保险箱都有一个回厂修复密码
All these electronic safes have manufacturer override codes.
我有一个认识的人能帮我们
I have a guy who can get them for us. One of them will work.
要多久
How long?
那看要多久才能打通他的电话
Depends on how long it takes to get him on the phone.
大卫 我们可能有办法了
David, we may have just found a way.
那最好 没多少时间
You'd better. You are running out of time.
疑犯用钛金属固定住仪器以防泄露
The suspect has used a titanium clamp to secure the device to a railing.
我们正在拆除它
We are defusing on the site.
威尔逊 你那边情况怎么?
Wilson, what's your status?
抓获疑犯
The suspect's in custody.
纽约时报的记者就在边上 病毒安全
New York Times' men's around. Virus is contained.
喂
Yeah.
西雅图和拉斯维加斯已经安全 丹佛那个在打电话的时候被击毙
Seattle, Las Vegas' secured, Denver's suspect's taken down making a phone call.
好 等等
Ok, hold on.
杰克 拉斯维加斯和西雅图的运输人已被抓获
Jack, we got the couriers in Las Vegas and Seattle without incident.
但是丹佛那个被击毙前还在打电话
But Saunders man in Denver was making a phone call when he was killed.
电话打出去了吗? 有没有让他给其他人通风报信?
Did he complete the call? Did he warn the other couriers?
不知道
We don't know.
我们会查清楚的
We got to find that out.
克萝伊 我刚刚收到从洛杉矶传过来的2级卫星图像
Chloe, I am getting a level 2 SAT transmission from the LA grid.
你确定? 坐标是多少?
Are you sure? What are the coordinates?
阿尔法 1733和德尔塔 401
Alpha 1733 at Delta 401.
那是市中心 马上进行卫星定位
That's downtown. Lock in on the SAT field.
好了
It's done.
传到我的屏幕上来
Transfer to my screen.
好
Ok.
我是杰克
This is Jack.
杰克 我是克萝伊
Jack, it's Chloe.
你有什么新发现?
What do you got?
桑德斯没说谎
Saunders is telling the truth.
拉本斯就在洛杉矶
Rabens is in Los Angeles.
哪?
Where?
他在南弗劳尔大街 正向西北移动
He's on south Flower heading northwest.
找到他了
We got a location.
跟紧他的行进路线
I want you to extrapolate his path.
标注出可能受袭的目标
Cross reference it with a list of probably public targets.
好
Already done.
最有可能的地方就是加利福尼亚中心
The most likely match is the California Center.
很有可能
A mall makes sense.
派警察过去疏散群众并维持秩序 我们正赶过去
I want you to get units over there to evacuate and secure the area. We are on our way.
我刚才想见托尼
I just tried to see Tony.
警卫说你禁止我进去
Security said you are denying me access.
他现在是罪犯 米歇尔
He's a prisoner, Michelle.
我是他妻子 他这么做都是为了救我
I'm his wife. He did what he did to save my life.
这我知道
I am aware of that.
就因为这样所以他现在面临叛国罪的指控
And because of that he's being charged with treason.
叛国?
Treason?
布拉德 听着 我知道他违反内部纪律擅自从反恐局带走简 桑德斯
Brad, look, I know that he broke protocol by taking Jane Saunders out of CTU,
但他是不会就这么把她交出去的
But he would never have given her up.
就因为他 我们才能抓到桑德斯
Because of him, we were able to catch Saunders.
两个小时前我们就该抓到桑德斯了 但是托尼帮他逃跑了
We had Saunders 2 hours ago, and Tony let him escape.
没人告诉你吗?
No one told you?
我们把桑德斯困在市区的一幢建筑里
We had Saunders trapped in a building downtown.
我们就要行动的时候 托尼把一支小队骗离预定位置 让桑德斯跑了
We were ready to drop the net, and Tony pulled unites out of position so Saunders could get away.
布拉德 那是没办法的选择
Brad, it was an impossible choice.
不 那不是
No, it wasn't.
托尼曾经宣誓有责任保护这个国家的公民
Tony has a sworn duty to protect the people of this country.
为了你而不顾他人就是叛国
Putting your life first was treasons.
他要为此被关进监狱
And he's going to prison for it.
布拉德.
Brad
我希望你能站在他的立场上想想 米歇尔
I want you to put yourself in his place, Michelle.
如果你也会作出同样的决定 你应该马上辞职
If you would have made the same call, you should resign right now.
目标还在以每小时40英里的速度向北移动
The target is still moving north at 40 miles per hour.
我们还要多久能拦截到他?
How long until we intercept?
1分钟左右
About a minute.
其他病毒情况怎么样?
How are we doing on the other vials?
他们已经抓获了华盛顿的首犯 还有其他两个
They got the Flagstaff couriers and the other 2 in Washington.
拉本斯是最后一个
Rabens is the last one.
好了 下个路口右转
Ok, make your next right.
你们应该就在他后面
You should be coming up right behind him.
好 我右转上了弗劳尔大街
Ok, I am turning right onto Flower.
目标离你们不到半个街区
The target is less than a block ahead of you.
你们应该能看见了
You should have a visual.
克萝伊 我们视线范围之内没有车
Chloe, there's no vehicles within range.
你确定目标还在车里?
Are you sure the targets still in the vehicle?
没错 他正以每小时40英里的速度前进
Of course, he's traveling 40 miles per hour.
你们接近了
You are closing.
目标在前方不到50英尺处
Target is less than 50 feet ahead of you.
我们前面没有车 克萝伊 复查你的信号
There's no cars in front of us, Chloe. You need to recheck your signals.
这不可能
It's not possible.
不 这有可能
Yes, it is.
他在我们下面
He's underneath us.
克萝伊 目标在地铁里
Chloe, the targets on the subway.
你能接入交通运输管理局的灾难应急系统吗?
Can you access the MTA's disaster response system?
可以 我能直接进入他们的中控机房
Yes, we can access their control center directly.
好的 我要让地铁在进站前就在隧道里停下来
Ok, we need to stop the train in the tunnel before it hits the station.
连入他们的系统
Logging onto their system.
亚当把拉本斯的拼图做出来了吗?
Has Adam been able to turn up a photo on Rabens yet?
没有 桑德斯还没完成辨认拼图
No, and Saunders hasn't completed the identity sketch.
好了 他们能接收我的请求将列车停在接近站台的隧道里
Ok, they're accepting my request to stop the train in the tunnel just short of the station.
要我通知交通运输管理局关闭车站吗?
Do you want me to tell MTA to close the station?
不 绝对不行
No, absolutely not.
如果让拉本斯察觉出有什么不妥 他有可能立即释放病毒
If Rabens notices anything out of the ordinary, he might release the virus.
我需要20名便衣探员和一支危险物品处理小队
I am going to need 20 personnel undercover and a backup HazMat team ASAP.
好的 已经联络附近的所有人
Okay, we've got men nearby.
我会通知哈蒙德下令部署
I will tell Hammond to order the redeployment.
喂 我是福克斯顿
Yeah, Foxton here.
搞到密码了
I've got this codes for the safe.
-好 先告诉我第一组  -676765#
-Ok, give me the first one.  -676765#
不行
That didn't work.
还有别的吗?
Got another one?
-快 快 快  -有 228767#
-Come on, come on, come on.  -Yeah 228767#
你听到了吗?
Did you hear that?
有车来了
There's a car coming.
不行
No.
雪莉回来了
Sherry is here.
听着 保持安静
Look, I need you to be quiet.
我们必须马上离开
We need to get the hell out of here.
安静
Quiet.
-下一组  -下一组是 352...
-The next one.  -The next one is 352...
该死 福克斯顿 快
Damn it, Foxton, come on.
成了
Got it.
不在这
It's not here.
好吧 不管了
All right, come on.
好了 我们走
That's it, let's go
什么?
What?
我绝对不会无功而返的
I didn't come this far to leave empty handed.
韦恩.
Wayne
这是怎么回事?
What's going on here?
回答我 这?
Answer me. What?
哦 现在我明白大卫为什么要约我见面了
Oh, now I understand why David wanted to meet me.
但我很惊讶你居然在这替他干这种肮脏的事
But I am so surprised to find you here doing his dirty work.
我可从没对不起你 韦恩
I have never done anything to hurt you, Wayne.
是大卫指使你的 对吗?
David put you up to this, didn't he?
雪莉 我...
Sherry, I...
回答我 大卫让你...
Answer me, David put...
由于某些原因 列车可能会晚点
There will be a short delay due to a stalled train ahead.
蔡斯 你的位置?
Chase, what's your location?
我在东面通道
I am covering the east side of the tracks.
明白
Copy that.
蔡斯 我看到你正下下楼
Chase, I've got a visual on you coming down the stairs.
交通运输管理局那边都准备好了吗?
Everything in place with the MTA?
他们已经准备好让列车进站了
They are ready to move the train into the station.
A队和B队就位了吗?
Team A and B, are you in position?
收到 我们已经就位
Roger. We are in position.
拉本斯的外貌特征
Rabens' description,
30多岁 白人男性 黑发 棕色眼睛 无明显特征
middle-thirty, white male, dark hair, brown eyes, none descript.
克萝伊 让列车进站
Chloe, release the train.
让列车进站
Release the hold on the train, release the train.
车门开启
Train doors are opening.
目标人物正在离开车厢
The target is moving off the train.
南面还是北面?
North or south?
北面
North.
目标向北面移动
Target is moving north.
所有小队 原地待命
All teams remain in your zones.
-克萝伊  -请讲
-Chloe.  -Go ahead.
你能定位目标的海拔高度吗?
Can you check the altitude on a GPS signal?
正在定位
If I triangulate.
没错 目标的海拔高度正在改变
Positive, target is changing altitude.
目标正在上楼
Target is moving upstairs.
至少有10个白人男性
There are 10 remaining white males.
目标正在向西移动
Target is now moving west.
A队 分散开 保持步调
Team A, split off and maintain pace.
目标任务正向南面移动
Target is now moving south.
目标正在向下移动
Target is now descending.
他正向第七大街出口移动
He's heading to the Seventh Street exit.
他正向你走去 杰克
Coming right towards you, Jack.
目标正向南移动
Target is heading south.
我发现4个白人男性
I got a visual. 4 white remaining males.
所有小组靠近
I want all teams to start closing in.
重复 所有小组靠近
I repeat, all teams start closing in.
怎么样了 克萝伊?
What have you got, Chloe?
目标正向西移动
Target is now moving west.
目标停止移动
Target has stopped moving.
The target has stopped.
目标确认
I have identification on the target.
6点钟方向的白人男性
White male at my 6 o'clock.
正在指路牌前看地图
He's looking at the map.
行动
I am initiating takedown.
把包放下
Drop the bag.
立刻趴下 不许动
Get on the ground, now. Don't move.
出什么事了?
What's going on?
东西在哪?
Where is it?
什么东西?
Where's what?
东西在哪?
Where is it?
蔡斯.
Chase
你们是什么人? 出什么事了?
What are you guys doing? What's going on?
有信号反应
I have got the signal.
要等危险物品处理小组吗
Should we wait for HazMat.
不用 病毒要么还在瓶子里 要么已经被污染了
No, it's either in the vial or we are already contaminated.
到底怎么了?
What is this?
这些东西不是我的 我甚至都...
Those aren't mine. I don't even...
闭嘴
Shut up.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
只是个发信器
It's just the transmitter.
这不是拉本斯
This isn't Rabens.
他知道我们在找他
He knows we are on to him.
病毒还在他手上
He's still got the vial.
立刻关闭车站 快
Shut the station down, now.
朱莉娅.
Julia
待在这 我马上回来
Stay here, I will be right back.
你去哪?
Where are you going?
你待在这就好了
Just stay here.
朱莉娅 你在这干嘛?
Julia, what are you doing here?
警察认为是我杀了艾伦
The police think I killed Alan.
嘿 我告诉过你什么都别说
Well, I told you to keep your mouth shut.
这事得怨你自己
It's nobody's fault but your own.
你拿着枪干什么?
What are you doing with a gun?
你不会这么做的
You don't want to do this.
因为你 我将会在监狱度过自己的余生
I am going to jail for the rest of my life because of you.
朱莉娅.
Julia
你不会的 朱莉娅
That isn't true, Julia.
不 等等 放轻松 万事好商量
No, wait. Relax. We're alright here.
你先把枪放下
You got to put that gun down.
不 不 进监狱的应该是她
No, no, she's the one who should be going to jail.
我这辈子都毁了 你还不明白吗?
My life is ruined, don't you understand that?
朱莉娅 求你了 肯定还有别的办法
Julia, please, we can, we can work this out.
他说的没错
He's right.
我们还有别的办法
We can work it out.
闭嘴 闭嘴
Shut up, shut up.
你一辈子都在说谎
You have been lying your entire life.
不过这次谎话可救不了你
You are not going to lie your way out of this.
你说的没错
You are right.
但现在 朱莉娅 我说的事实
But right now, Julia, I am telling you the truth.
我会替你向大卫求情 他会赦免你的
I will go to David and he will pardon you.
刚刚我还见过他 就在刚才
Now, I was just with him, just now.
我会再次成为他的夫人
I am going to be his wife again.
我说什么他都会听的
He will do whatever I say.
我保证 你绝对不会进监狱
I promise you, you will not spend one day in jail.
是不是这样 韦恩?
Isn't that so, Wayne?
朱莉娅 听着 你会得到你一直想要的东西
Julie, listen, you will have everything you have always wanted.
你可以自由生活 并继承艾伦的遗产
You will have your freedom, you'll have Alan's estate.
你想象一下 宝贝
You just think about it, sweetie.
我向你保证 你会好好的活着的
I promise, you will be set for life.
好 好 真是太好了
Good, good. That is real good.
真是太好了
That's good.
天啊 雪莉
My God. Sherry.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
不!
No!
哦 上帝啊 求你了 别这样
Oh, God, no, please.
守住站台尽头的位置
Take up position at the end of the platform.
杰克 我们已经截下车站里的所有人
Jack, we have detained everyone in the station.
我们及时关闭了车站
We shut it down in time.
列车进站后没有一个人离开
No ones left since the train came in.
好 派支队伍继续搜索上面的隧道
Ok, set up a team and start searching the tunnels.